Luis Horcajo

luishorcajomoreno@gmail.com +34636213629



ABOUT

I am a multidisciplinary designer with a unique perspective and strong problem solving skills. I aim to create a more socially engaged community by shaping digital experiences in both the cultural and commercial industries. I care about finding innovative solutions by deeply understanding the people around me and the worlds they live in.

EMPLOYMENT

MICHAEL KORS, GLASHÜTTE ORIGINAL & LOUIS VUITTON — SALES ADVISOR

November 2014 - January 2020

Offering personal advice to local and foreign customers, building customer loyalty and strategizing and rolled out initiatives to improve company standards and customer experience.

ADVIRA BEYOND, KUO EXPERIENCE & TELLING INSIGHT — COOLHUNTER

January 2009 - October 2014

Providing advice and perspective as a consumer and trendsetter to marketing companies, collaborating with them to create new product research, trends and ways of consumption.

VIERNES COMUNICACIÓN — JUNIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

October 2013 - October 2014

Working as the main graphic designer within a small team of three creative directors in the communication field, social innovation and inclusivity. Improving my visual designing skills, working with deadlines and growing in a team.

EDUCATION	TOOLS
IRONHACK — UX/UI DESIGN April 2020	Figma, Sketch, Invision, Principle, Adobe Creative Suite, HTML/CSS.
SALESIANOS — GRAPHIC DESIGN June 2015	SKILLS

English Spanish

LANGUAGES

Design & Innovation processes,
End-to-end & iterative design, Research,
Usability Testing, Design Thinking.